Guide to the Creative Time Archive 1973-2006 MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Video and Film, 107335
  - Subseries A: Video Recordings - Access Copies, 107629
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, 6/16/88 (3rd row, tight in), 1988; 107825 (Case 179.0407)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, 6/18/88 (3rd Row Wide Shot), 1988; 107824 (Case 179.0152)
    - Marcos Kurtycz, "Organikwars" 12/8/88-12/10/88; "Organrites" 12/8/88; "One Dos Tres O!" 12/9/88; "Clavarte" 12/10/88, 1988; 107823 (Case 179.0459)
      Duration: 01:47:00
    - SRL [Survival Research Laboratories], Shea Stadium 5/19/88; CBS News 5/17/88 [Press], 107822 (Case 179.0465)
      Duration: 00:08:00
    - Survival Research [Laboratories], [1988]; 107821 (Case 179.0603)
    - Survival Research Laboratories, [1988]; 107820 (Case 179.0553)
      Duration: 01:00:00
    - Tony Fisher, Steven Ausbury, "The Lost Opera", 1988; 107819 (Case 179.0463)
      Duration: 00:06:00
    - Dumb Type, "pH" 1990, "Pleasure Life" 1988, 1988, 1990; 107818 (Case 179.0541)
      Duration: 00:58:00
    - Merry Conway, Noni Pratt, "As a Dream That Vanishes" 1991; "In the Eye of the Beholder" 1988, 1988, 1991; 107817 (Case 179.0461)
      Duration: 01:30:00
    - "Desire Borne", 1989; 107816 (Case 179.0382)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Jessie Jane Lewis, "Blind Ally", 6/22/89, 1989; 107815 (Case 179.0178)
    - Leni Schwendinger, "Light Site-ings", 11/1/89, 1989; 107814 (Case 179.0266)
    - Mark Pauline, 1989 Sculpture Grant Award Exhibition, San Francisco Artspace, July 11-Aug 19, 1989 (Dir. Jonathan Reiss and Leslie Asako Gladsjo), 107813 (Case 179.0601)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Karen Finley, "3 Parables and 2 Testimonies", 9/28/90, 1990; 107812 (Case 179.0192)
      Duration: 00:40:00
    - HIV TV, Swarthmore College, 12/16/90, 1990; 107811 (Case 179.0521)
      Duration: 00:44:00
    - John Kelly, "Love of a Poet", 10/19/90, 107810 (Case 179.0437)
    - Kit-Yin Snyder, Enrico IV Set/Installation - Creative Media Conc., 9/25/90, 1990; 107809 (Case 179.0435)
    - The Bowery Concert, 9/15/90 (4 PM show), 1990; 107808 (Case 179.0417)
    - "Clean Needles Save Lives", [1991]; 107807 (Case 179.0527)
    - "Needle Exchange" (without credits), [1991]; 107806 (Case 179.0529)
      Duration: 00:31:00
    - Dumb Type, "pH", Kyoto Municipal Museum of the Arts, Institute Contemporary Arts, Nagoya, Spring 1991, 107805 (Case 179.0537)
      Duration: 01:10:00
    - Dumb Type, "pH", [1991]; 107804 (Case 179.0539)
      Duration: 01:01:00
    - Dumb Type, "pH", [1991]; 107803 (Case 179.0543)
    - Fear of Disclosure - Ellen Spiro, Marina Alvarez, "(In)Visible Women", [1991]; 107802 (Case 179.0445)
      Duration: 00:27:00
    - Jordi Torrent, "Honeymoon", 1991; 107801 (Case 179.0439)
    - Antoni Miraldi, "Honeymoon Project" (cued for 10 minute viewing segment, parts I and II), [1991]; 107800 (Case 179.0142)
    - La Fura Dels Baus, "Suz/O/Suz", 4/1/91, 1991; 107799 (Case 179.0186)
    - "Transitions Inc.", 5/9/92, 1992; 107798 (Case 179.0441)
      Duration: 00:41:00
    - Fear of Disclosure - Marlon Riggs, "Non, Je Ne Regrette Rien", 1992; 107797 (Case 179.0447)
      Duration: 00:48:00
    - Jordi Torrent, "Monuments in Love", 1992; 107796 (Case 179.0140)
      Duration: 00:30:00
    - "Patina Du Prey's Memorial Dress", Hunter Reynolds, ICA Boston, 1993; 107795 (Case 179.0511)
      Duration: 00:28:00
    - 42nd Street Art Project - Interviews, 1993; 107794 (Case 179.0487)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - News All Evening NY 1 6/21/93; News All Morning NY 1 7/30/93; Good Day NY 7/6/93; Daybreak CNN 7/10/93; Channel 9 News 8/2/93; MTV News 8/11/93; NY Views 8/14/93 [Press], 1993; 107793 (Case 179.0473)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - TV coverage, interviews [Press], 1993; 107792 (Case 179.0398)
      Duration: 00:34:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - Elizabeth Streb, Dyke TV, Episode 19, 1993; 107791 (Case 179.0505)
      Duration: 00:45:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - Elizabeth Streb, Ringside, "Kid Action", 1993; 107790 (Case 179.0244)
      Duration: 00:12:00
    - Debra Levine, "Hairy Tales", [1993]; 107789 (Case 179.0443)
    - Dyke TV Arts Compilation, 1993; 107788 (Case 179.0509)
    - Dyke TV, Episodes 1 and 3, 1993; 107787 (Case 179.0507)
    - Glenn Belverio, "Two Spirits Speak Out", 1993; 107786 (Case 179.0264)
    - Nelson Rodriguez, "HIV: A Home Video" (Draft #2), "13 Years" (Draft #3), "HIV: A Home Video" (Draft #4), 1993; 107785 (Case 179.0519)
      Duration: 00:24:00
    - Thomas Allen Harris, "Heaven Earth and Hell", 1993; 107784 (Case 179.0366)
    - Creative Time: 20 Years of Art in Unexpected Places, 1994; ID: 179.0738; 162981 (Case 179.0738)
    - 20 Years of Art in Unexpected Places, Dyke TV, 7/94, 1994; 107783 (Case 179.0358)
    - 20 Years of Art in Unexpected Places, Dyke TV, 7/94, 1994; 107782 (Case 179.0431)
    - Creative Time 20th Anniversary Celebration, 1994; ID: 179.0741; 162983 (Case 179.0741)
      Duration: 00:50:00
    - Creative Time 20th Anniversary Celebration The Apollo Theater July 7, 1994 (tape 2 of 2), ID: 179.0744; 162985 (Case 179.0744)
      Duration: 00:42:00
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration (tape 1), 1994; 107781 (Case 179.0392)
      Original Format: HI 8
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration (tape 2), 1994; 107780 (Case 179.0394)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration, 7/7/94 (tape 1 of 2), 1994; 107779 (Case 179.0609)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration, 7/7/94 (tape 2 of 2), 1994; 107778 (Case 179.0364)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration, 7/7/94 (tape 3), 1994; 107777 (Case 179.0396)
    - Anniversary Party Interviews, [1994]; 107776 (Case 179.0485)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - PBS Video, MacNeil Lehrer News Hour, 9/23/94 [Press], 1994; 107775 (Case 179.0475)
    - Dyke TV, Best of Winter '94, 1994; 107774 (Box not specified, Folder ID: 179.0517)
      Duration: 00:51:00
    - Martha Wilson, Joyce Scott, Blondell Cummings, Reno, Carnival Knowledge, "Body Politics", 2/14/94, 1994; 107773 (Case 179.0513)
      Duration: 01:36:00
    - Martha Wilson, Mary Ellen Strom, Peggy Pettitt, Holly Hughes, "Body Politics", 2/15/94, 1994; 107772 (Case 179.0384)
      Duration: 01:26:00
    - Rebecca Bollinger, "Alphabetically Sorted", 1994; 107771 (Case 179.0202)
    - Use Mass Transit - Hey Bozo! TV Coverage [Press], [1994]; 107770 (Case 179.0252)
    - Thomas Allen Harris, "Vintage: Families of Value" documentary, 1995; 107769 (Case 179.0256)
      Duration: 00:01:00
    - VAPP 1995 Application - Gretchen Bender, "Still/Here", "Total Recall"; Ron Kuivila, "VR on $5/Day; Frank Mann, "A Timely Existence"; Grahame Weinbren: "Sonata", "The Erl King", 107768 (Case 179.0262)
    - Art in the Anchorage - EAR, Harmony Rockets, 1996; 107767 (Case 179.0216)
    - Music in the Anchorage (demo reel), 1996; 107766 (Case 179.0156)
    - Paco Cao, "Rent A Body", Carol and Marylyn TV Talk Show, [1996]; 107765 (Case 179.0467)
      Duration: 00:35:00
    - Pierrick Sorin, "A Very Full Life", et. al., [1996]; 107764 (Case 179.0158)
    - Adrianne Wortzel, "Technoseduction Exhibition", "My Robotic", "The Ship's Detective" projection installation, [1997]; 107763 (Case 179.0160)
    - Ange Leccia, "Sabatina", 1997; 107762 (Case 179.0411)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage - Rough Footage, 9/11/97, 1997; 107761 (Case 179.0170)
    - Magali Claude, "Tiems. Toi droit", "Les Gestes du Travail", "La Chora. Les rumours", 1997; 107760 (Case 179.0491)
    - "ATM Art" (5/98), "Gesture as Value" (6/98), BBC [Press], 1998; 107759 (Case 179.0304)
    - Ange Leccia, "ISA", 1998; 107758 (Case 179.0380)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Detroit Techno, 1998; 107757 (Case 179.0162)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Standard and Poor, "Big Night Out", 6/18/98, 1998; 107756 (Case 179.0168)
    - Jerelyn Hanrahan, "Gesture as Value", [1998]; 107755 (Case 179.0306)
    - Jeremy Dawson, Richard Gordon, Creative Time commercial loop, 11/2/98, 1998; 107754 (Case 179.0390)
      Original Format: Beta
    - Jeremy Dawson, Richard Gordon, Creative Time commercial, 11/2/98, 1998; 107753 (Case 179.0409)
    - Jeremy Dawson, Richard Gordon, Creative Time commercial loop, [1998]; 107752 (Case 179.0388)
    - "Between Dreams and History", Installation Video (dir. Christopher Beaver), [1998]; 107751 (Case 179.0531)
    - Shimon Attie, "Between Dreams and History", BBC, Fall 1998, 107750 (Case 179.0533)
    - Shimon Attie, "Between Dreams and History" (installation version, dir. Christopher Beaver), [1998]; 107749 (Case 179.0535)
      Duration: 00:43:00
    - The Art Guys with Todd Oldham, "Suits: The Clothes Make the Man", 11/2/98, 1998; 107748 (Case 179.0573)
    - The Art Guys, [1998]; 107747 (Case 179.0579)
    - The Art Guys, CBS [Press], [1998]; 107746 (Case 179.0583)
      Duration: 00:10:00
    - "F.R.E.D." Projections, Fall 1999 (shot by Roberto Guerra), 107745 (Case 179.0625)
      Original Format: MiniDV
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged" (fashion video looped) 5/18/99, 1999; 107744 (Case 179.0298)
      Duration: 02:10:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged" (film video looped) 5/18/99, 1999; 107743 (Case 179.0300)
      Duration: 02:00:00
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged", [1999]; 107742 (Case 179.0126)
    - Courtney Harmel, Brooklyn Library Projections, 11/6/99 (Tape 1), 1999; 107741 (Case 179.0194)
    - Standard and Poor, Carpet Rollers, Park Restaurant, 2/2/99, 1999; 107740 (Case 179.0250)
    - The Art Guys, Fashion TV [Press], 1999; 107739 (Case 179.0581)
    - The 59th Minute - Genevieve Cadieux, "Portrait", 1999-2000; 107738 (Case 179.0280)
    - [Art in the Anchorage] - Granular Synthesis, "Noise Gate" (Prod. Footage), [2000]; 107737 (Case 179.0188)
    - "Tibor in Orbit", Times Square, May-June, 2000, 107736 (Case 179.0276)
    - Bus Tour, 9/27/00, 2000; 107735 (Case 179.0292)
    - Chris Doyle, "Leap", 2000; 107734 (Case 179.0455)
      Duration: 00:11:00
    - Chris Doyle, "Leap", Apr 27-30, 2000, 107733 (Case 179.0449)
      Duration: 00:04:00
    - Chris Doyle, "Leap" (Demo), [2000]; 107732 (Case 179.0451)
    - "Leap", [2000]; 107731 (Case 179.0515)
    - "Leap", Dec[ember], [2000]; 107730 (Case 179.0453)
    - "Leap", Interviews, [2000]; 107729 (Case 179.0457)
      Duration: 00:33:00
    - The 59th Minute - "Tibor in Orbit", 4/4/00, 2000; 107728 (Case 179.0352)
    - "Leap", "Tribute in Light", "Tap", "59th Minute" (show reel), [2000-2002]; 107727 (Case 179.0419)
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Massless Medium: Explorations Sensory Immersion", 2001; 107726 (Case 179.0172)
    - Hans Haacke, May 12, 2001, 107725 (Case 179.0246)
    - Music in the Anchorage - 6/21/01 (rough footage), 2001; 107724 (Case 179.0647)
    - [Music in the Anchorage] - Porter Ricks, SND, 6/28 (#3), [2001]; 107723 (Case 179.0619)
      Duration: 00:57:00
    - [Music in the Anchorage] - Porter Ricks, Thomas Heckman, 6/28 (#4), [2001]; 107722 (Case 179.0621)
    - [Music in the Anchorage] 6/28 #3, [2001]; 107721 (Case 179.0623)
    - Noam Toran, "Object for Lonely Men", Blur, 2001; 107720 (Case 179.0559)
    - Rachel Stevens, NAAMP Portfolio Presentation, 12/01, 2001; 107719 (Case 179.0429)
    - The 59th Minute - Bruce and Norman Yonemoto, "ahistory", Oct 19-Nov 30, 2001, 107718 (Case 179.0348)
    - The 59th Minute - Gary Hill, Michael Snow, Mary Lucier, "Fast Forward", 12/2/2001-1/27/02, 107717 (Case 179.0370)
    - The 59th Minute - Marco Brambilla, "Superstar", Feb 28-Apr 15, 2001, 107716 (Case 179.0354)
    - The 59th Minute - Marco Brambilla, "Superstar"; Fischli and Weiss, "Cat Drinking Milk"; William Kentridge, "Shadow", 2001; 107715 (Case 179.0258)
    - The 59th Minute - Michael Snow, "Fridge", 2001; 107714 (Case 179.0479)
    - "Out of the Ashes", "Towers of Light", Dateline, 10/21/01 [Press], 2001; 107712 (Case 179.0493)
    - "Out of the Ashes", Dateline, 10/21/01 [Press], 2001; 107711 (Case 179.0288)
    - The 59th Minute - Fischli and Weiss, "Cat Drinking Milk"; William Kentridge, "Shadows"; Bruce and Norman Yonemoto, "ahistory"; Jeff Gibson, "Viralysis"; Gary Hill, "Liminal Object"; Mary Lucier, "Monarch"; Michael Snow, "Fridge"; Genevieve Cadieux, "Portrait", [2001]; 107713 (Case 179.0481)
    - Memorials, CBS Evening News, 12/11/01 [Press], 2001; 107710 (Case 179.0282)
    - "Tribute in Light" press conference, 3/6/02 (part 1 of 2) [Press], 2002; 107709 (Case 179.0425)
    - "Tribute in Light", Anne Pasternak, Pure Oxygen, 3/12/02 [Press], 2002; 107708 (Case 179.0551)
    - "Tribute in Light", Nippon Television, Tokyo, 3/9/02 [Press], 2002; 107707 (Case 179.0423)
    - "Tribute in Light", Nippon Television, Tokyo, 3/9/02 [Press], 2002; 107706 (Case 179.0547)
    - "Tribute in Light", Press Conference (tape 2 of 2) [Press], 2002; 107705 (Case 179.0549)
    - "Tribute in Light", Pure Oxygen, 4/10/02 (Segment B) [Press], 2002; 107704 (Case 179.0427)
    - "Tribute in Light", CNN, Towers of Light [Press], [2002]; 107703 (Case 179.0545)
    - "Tribute in Light", Illumina TV, ArtsWorld [Press], [2002]; 107702 (Case 179.0495)
    - "Tribute in Light", NY One [Press], [2002]; 107701 (Case 179.0497)
      Format: DVD-R,
    - "Tribute in Light", Towers of Light, Proun Space Studio, [2002]; 107700 (Case 179.0499)
    - Therese Cafaro, Jayson Haedrich, "Tribute: A Documentary", [2002]; 107699 (Case 179.0421)
    - Everton Sylvester, Skylight Gallery, 9/5/02 (Tape 2), 2002; 107698 (Case 179.0154)
    - Everton Sylvester, Skylight Gallery, 9/5/02 (Tape 4), 2002; 107697 (Case 179.0166)
    - Everton Sylvester, 9/5/02 (tape 1), 2002; 107696 (Case 179.0641)
    - Everton Sylvester, 9/5/02 (tape 3), 2002; 107695 (Case 179.0631)
    - Gabri SI High School 9/13/02 (2 of 2), 2002; 107694 (Case 179.0615)
    - Gabri SI High School, 9/13/02 (1 of 2), 2002; 107693 (Case 179.0649)
      Duration: 00:39:00
    - Holiday Light Show - Grand Central Project, Comp Reel, [2002]; 107692 (Case 179.0286)
    - James Buckhouse, Holly Brubach, "Tap" - Tech TV (30 second spot), 6/12/2002 [Press], 107691 (Case 179.0284)
    - "Sonic Garden", NY Tonight [Press], [2002]; 107690 (Case 179.0296)
    - Stephanie Simon, "Poster Project", 2/02, 2002; 107689 (Case 179.0268)
    - Toshi, 8/28/02 (1 of 2), 2002; 107688 (Case 179.0633)
    - Toshi, 8/28/02 (2 of 2), 2002; 107687 (Case 179.0617)
    - William Wegman - [The 59th Minute] Fox Good Day Live, 11/18/02 [Press], 2002; 107686 (Case 179.0374)
    - Adelle Lutz, "The Peace Piece", [2003]; 107685 (Case 179.0605)
    - Artist Roundtable (final group discussion), 8/5/03, 2003; 107684 (Case 179.0136)
    - Artist Roundtable (Vardit's Group), 8/5/03, 2003; 107683 (Case 179.0150)
    - Artists Roundtable, Vardit, [2003]; 107682 (Case 179.0503)
    - Artist Roundtable, Carol's Group, 8/5/03, 2003; 107681 (Case 179.0639)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Gunpowder", drawings at Grucci, 8/7/03, 2003; 107680 (Case 179.0635)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Light Cycle", 2003; 107679 (Case 179.0274)
    - [Cai Guo-Qiang], "Light Cycle", "Aerial", [2003]; 107678 (Case 179.0190)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Light Cycle", [2003]; 107677 (Case 179.0637)
    - Focus Group, 3/24/03 (1 of 2), 2003; 107676 (Case 179.0643)
    - Focus Group, 3/24/03 (2 of 2), 2003; 107675 (Case 179.0645)
    - The 59th Minute - Thomas Struth, 2003; 107674 (Case 179.0386)
    - [The 59th Minute] - Thomas Struth, "Video Portraits": Kim Heirston, Thomas Gutt, Anne Grefe, Rafael Hartmann, [2003]; 107673 (Case 179.0607)
    - Thomas Struth Exhibit, German television, 2/4/03 [Press], 2003; 107672 (Case 179.0362)
    - CBS Sunday Morning, "Freedom of Expression", 7/4/04 [Press], 2004; 107671 (Case 179.0294)
    - Freedom of Expression [Monument], 11/04, 2004; 107670 (Case 179.0489)
    - Jenny Holzer, "For New York City" (1), 2004; 107669 (Case 179.0585)
    - Jenny Holzer, "For New York City" (2), 2004; 107668 (Case 179.0593)
    - Jenny Holzer, "For The City" (raw footage), [2004]; 107667 (Case 179.0587)
    - "For New York City", '04, Xenon Projections at Bethesda Fountain, Central Park, 10/27/04 (tape 4), 2004; 107666 (Case 179.0591)
    - O and A [Sam Auinger and Bruce Odland], "Blue Moon", Stephanie Simon 5/04 [Press], 2004; 107665 (Case 179.0471)
    - The 59th Minute - "Dream Sequence", "Dwelling", "Mousetrap" 1/18/04, 2004; 107664 (Case 179.0308)
    - The 59th Minute - Carlos Amorales, "The Forest", 10/28/04, 2004; 107663 (Case 179.0310)
    - The 59th Minute - Gunther Selichar, [2004]; 107662 (Case 179.0248)
    - The 59th Minute - Hiraki Sawa, "Dwelling"; Janaina Tschape, "Dream Sequence", Jan 21-May 16, 2004, 107661 (Case 179.0378)
    - The 59th Minute - Hiraki Sawa, "Dwelling"; Janaina Tschape, "Dream Sequence", Jan 21-May 16, 2004, 107660 (Case 179.0415)
    - The 59th Minute - [Carlos] Amorales, Televisa New York, [2004-2005]; 107659 (Case 179.0483)
    - Anne Pasternak, Stephanie Simon, 2/05 [Press], 2005; 107658 (Case 179.0270)
    - Dreamland Artist Club - Stephanie Simon, 2005; 107657 (Case 179.0130)
    - Jenny Holzer, Bobst Library, NYU, 11/16/05, 2005; 107656 (Case 179.0589)
    - Jenny Holzer, Political Art (edit), Reuters, Fall 2005, 107655 (Case 179.0595)
    - Song Dong, "Evaporating Art", Reuters, 2005; 107654 (Case 179.0372)
    - "Living With AIDS: Seize Control of the FDA", Undated; 107653 (Case 179.0523)
    - # 4, 6/28, Undated; 107652 (Case 179.0146)
    - [unidentified], Undated; 107651 (Case 179.0164)
      Duration: 00:47:00
    - [unidentified], Undated; 107650 (Case 179.0555)
    - 1st Tape "R", Undated; 107649 (Case 179.0200)
    - Ange Leccia, Undated; 107648 (Case 179.0360)
    - Art on the Beach 1, Undated; ID: 179.0726; 162962 (Case 179.0726)
      Physical Characteristics and Techincal Requirements Note
    - Art on the Beach, Undated; ID: 179.0711; 162940 (Case 179.0711)
    - Art on the Beach / School of Hard Knocks, Undated; ID: 179.0708; 162937 (Case 179.0708)
    - 2 Art on the Beach School of Hard Knocks, Undated; ID: 179.0735; 162977 (Case 179.0735)
    - Art on the Beach (Creative Time Master), Undated; ID: 179.0702; 162917 (Case 179.0702)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 1), Undated; 107647 (Case 179.0330)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 2, Kay Lynn), Undated; 107646 (Case 179.0344)
    - Art on the Beach Kay Lynn 2, Undated; ID: 179.0729; 162966 (Case 179.0729)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 3, Kay Lynn), Undated; 107645 (Case 179.0356)
    - Art on the Beach Kay Lynn 3, Undated; ID: 179.0732; 162970 (Case 179.0732)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 5), Undated; 107644 (Case 179.0376)
    - Bill Shannon, Axis Dance and Solo, Undated; 107643 (Case 179.0368)
    - Burlesque Video, 2 Versions, Undated; 107642 (Case 179.0433)
    - Dreamland Artist Club, Undated; 107641 (Case 179.0132)
    - Fair and Balanced News/ Freedom, Undated; 107640 (Case 179.0525)
      Duration: [1]--00:02:00 [2]--00:06:00 [3]--00:51:00
    - Grand Central Installation, Undated; 107639 (Case 179.0138)
    - Grand Central Installation, Undated; 107638 (Case 179.0198)
      Duration: 01:07:00
    - Grand Central Installation, Undated; 107637 (Case 179.0627)
      Duration: 01:02:00
    - Granular Synthesis, Undated; 107636 (Case 179.0174)
    - Kathy Brew, Roberto Guerra, DNAID, Undated; 107635 (Case 179.0272)
    - Marjetica Potrc, "Borders" (Tape 1), Undated; 107634 (Case 179.0180)
    - Marjetica Potrc, "Borders" (tape 2, beginning of general discussion), Undated; 107633 (Case 179.0629)
      Duration: 01:21:00
    - Peter Freusen Descartes Video, Undated; ID: 179.0774; 163010 (Case 179.0774)
    - Ringside, Undated; ID: 179.0696; 162909 (Case 179.0696)
    - Susan Cianciolo, "Diadel", Undated; 107632 (Case 179.0182)
    - William Kentridge, Undated; 107631 (Case 179.0260)
    - Zhang Huan, Undated; 107630 (Case 179.0128)
    - Masstransiscope by Bill Brand, 1980; ID: 179.0776; 210121 (Case 179.0776)
      Original Format: Unknown
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Originals, 107338
    - Liz Phillips, Installations Documentary Compilation, 1970-1999, 107628 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0675)
      Format: Format: VHS
      Duration: [25 min.]
    - Big Apple Minute, Ruckus Manhattan [Press], 1976; 107627 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0311)
      Format: Format: 3/4" video cassette
    - Art on the Beach (aerial videotaping by Joe Kos), 1978; 107626 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0323)
      Format: 3/4" video cassette
    - Art on the Beach (video by Joe Kos), 1978; 107625 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0277)
    - [Custom and Culture] - Jim Pomeroy, 5/31/79, 1979; 107624 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0695)
      Format: Format: Betamax
      Duration: [Unknown]
    - [Custom and Culture] - Kenneth Rinker, Dancers, 5/20/79, 1979; 107623 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0694)
    - [Custom and Culture] - Stuart Sherman, 6/8/79; Laurie Anderson and Peter Gordon, 6/14/79, 1979; 107622 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0696)
    - SRL [Survival Research Laboratories], TV Spots, 6/86, 6/81, 9/89, 11/83 [Press], 1981, 1983, 1986, 1989; 107621 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0556)
      Format: VHS
    - Alice Farley, "The Water Garden" - Cooper-Hewitt Museum, 8/82, 1982; 107620 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0237)
    - Art on the Beach - Danny McCusker, "Art in the Anchorage with Warhol", "Big Apple Minutes", 1982; 107619 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0239)
    - Tannis Hugill, "Hanging Woman", "Flagella: A Space Probe", 1982-1984; 107618 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0687)
      Format: 3/4" Umatic
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, "Drunken Madness", 1983; 107617 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0241)
    - Art on the Beach - Live at 5, 5/13/83 [Press], 1983; 107616 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0476)
    - Magnificent Force, Panache, Sesame St., 9/1983, 107615 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0690)
    - Art on the Beach - 1984 highlights (Dan Freel, edited master 2/8/85), 107614 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0412)
    - Art on the Beach - MTV, 7/7/84-9/16/84 [Press], 1984; 107613 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0651)
    - Art on the Beach (highlight reel), 1984; 107612 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0315)
    - Art in the Anchorage - "The Memory Theater of Giulio Camillo", 1985; 107611 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0203)
    - Art on the Beach - Yoshiko Chuma, Lenny Pickett, Fred Wilson, 1985; 107610 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0321)
    - Art on the Beach - "School of Hard Knocks" (tape 2), [1985]; 107609 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0331)
    - Art on the Beach - "School of Hard Knocks" (tape 3), [1985]; 107608 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0319)
    - Art on the Beach - "School of Hard Knocks" (tape 7), [1985]; 107607 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0317)
    - Art on the Beach - Yoshiko Chuma, "School of Hard Knocks", [1985]; 107606 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0313)
    - Art on the Beach (CBC Master #1), 1985; 107605 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0325)
    - Art on the Beach (CBC Master #2), 1985; 107604 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0327)
    - Marianne Goldberg, "Environs" (excerpts), 1985; 107603 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0689)
    - Subway Art, Live From Underground, 9/29/85 (2), 1985; 107602 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0652)
    - Subway Art, Live From Underground (3), [1985]; 107601 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0653)
    - Subway Art, Live From Underground, 9/29/85 (4), 1985; 107600 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0654)
    - Subway Art, Live From Underground, 9/29/85-9/30/85 (5), 1985; 107599 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0655)
    - Subway Art, Live From Underground, 9/29/85 (7), 1985; 107598 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0656)
    - Subway Art (8), [1985]; 107597 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0657)
    - Subway Art (9), [1985]; 107596 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0658)
    - Subway Art (10), [1985]; 107595 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0659)
    - [Subway Art] (11), [1985]; 107594 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0660)
    - Survival Research Laboratories, "Virtues of Negative Fascination", 1985-1986; 107593 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0677)
      Duration: [80 min.]
    - Survival Research Laboratories (Mark Pauline, Matt Heckert, Eric Werner), "The Virtues of Negative Fascination", [1985-1986]; 107592 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0598)